Guide to the The Exit Art Archive 1982 - 2011 MSS 343
© 2012 Fales Library and Special Collections
- Series I: Exhibition Files
  - Paradise 8 [1999.01]: Curator/Artist File - Ingrid Schaffner, 1998 - 2000 (Box 71, Folder 2)
  - Paradise 8 [1999.01]: Curator/Artist File - Franklin Sirmins, 1998 - 1999 (Box 71, Folder 3)
  - Paradise 8 [1999.01]: Curator/Artist File - Henry Urbach, 1998 - 1999 (Box 71, Folder 4)
  - Paradise 8 [1999.01]: Curator/Artist File - Martha Wilson, 1998 - 1999 (Box 71, Folder 5)
  - Paradise 8 [1999.01]: Public Programs - Performances, January 23, 1999 (Box 71, Folder 6)
  - Paradise 8 [1999.01]: Guest Book (Box 71, Folder 7)
  - Paradise 8 [1999.01]: Press Clippings (Box 71, Folder 8)
  - The Stroke [1999.02]: Invitations, May 1, 1999 (Box 71, Folder 9)
  - The Stroke [1999.02]: Press Release, May 1, 1999 (Box 71, Folder 10)
  - The Stroke [1999.02]: Research, 1993 (Box 71, Folder 11)
  - The Stroke [1999.02]: NEA Application, Curator List, Studio Visits, 1994, 1999 (Box 71, Folder 12)
  - The Stroke [1999.02]: Exhibition Checklist and Map, May 1, 1999 (Box 71, Folder 13)
  - The Stroke [1999.02]: Price List (Box 71, Folder 14)
  - The Stroke [1999.02]: Correspondence (Box 71, Folder 15)
  - The Stroke [1999.02]: Loan Information (Box 71, Folder 16)
  - The Stroke [1999.02]: Shipping Information (Box 72, Folder 1)
  - The Stroke [1999.02]: Wall Text/Sign (Box 72, Folder 2)
  - The Stroke [1999.02]: Curator/Artist File - Ross Bleckner (Box 72, Folder 3)
  - The Stroke [1999.02]: Curator/Artist File - Carroll Dunham (Box 72, Folder 4)
  - The Stroke [1999.02]: Curator/Artist File - Ellen Gallagher (Box 72, Folder 5)
  - The Stroke [1999.02]: Curator/Artist File - Kerry James Marshall (Box 72, Folder 6)
  - The Stroke [1999.02]: Curator/Artist File - Suzanne McClelland, 1996, 1999 (Box 72, Folder 7)
  - The Stroke [1999.02]: Curator/Artist File - Elizabeth Murray (Box 72, Folder 8)
  - The Stroke [1999.02]: Curator/Artist File - Lari Pittman (Box 72, Folder 9)
  - The Stroke [1999.02]: Curator/Artist File - David Reed (Box 72, Folder 10)
  - The Stroke [1999.02]: Curator/Artist File - Shahzia Sikander (Box 72, Folder 11)
  - The Stroke [1999.02]: Film/Video Research (Box 72, Folder 12)
  - The Stroke [1999.02]: Public Programs - Artists' Talk, May - June 1999 (Box 72, Folder 13)
  - The Stroke [1999.02]: Press Clippings (Box 72, Folder 14)
  - Little Kino in Slumberland [1999.03]: Invitations, Administrative, July 17 - 18, 1999 (Box 72, Folder 15)
  - Monumental Drawings [1999.04]: Research (Box 72, Folder 16)
  - Monumental Drawings [1999.04]: Invitations, August - September 1999 (Box 72, Folder 17)
  - Monumental Drawings [1999.04]: Press Release, September 18, 1999 (Box 72, Folder 18)
  - Monumental Drawings [1999.04]: Exhibition Preparation/Installation Information, August - September 1999 (Box 72, Folder 19)
  - Monumental Drawings [1999.04]: Correspondence (Box 72, Folder 20)
  - Monumental Drawings [1999.04]: Loan Information (Box 72, Folder 21)
  - Monumental Drawings [1999.04]: Exhibition Checklist (Box 72, Folder 22)
  - Monumental Drawings [1999.04]: Price List (Box 72, Folder 23)
  - Monumental Drawings [1999.04]: Artist Files (Box 72, Folder 24)
  - Monumental Drawings [1999.04]: Wall Text/Signs (Box 72, Folder 25)
  - Monumental Drawings [1999.04]: Slide Script (Box 72, Folder 26)
  - Monumental Drawings [1999.04]: Press Clippings (Box 72, Folder 27)
  - Choice 99 [1999.05]: Invitations, September - November 1999 (Box 73, Folder 1)
  - Choice 99 [1999.05]: Press Release, November 13, 1999 (Box 73, Folder 2)
  - Choice 99 [1999.05]: Exhibition Preparation/Installation Information, November 1999 (Box 73, Folder 3)
  - Choice 99 [1999.05]: Exhibition Checklist, November 13, 1999 (Box 73, Folder 4)
  - Choice 99 [1999.05]: Price List, November 13, 1999 (Box 73, Folder 5)
  - Choice 99 [1999.05]: Correspondence, 1999 - 2000 (Box 73, Folder 6)
  - Choice 99 [1999.05]: Loan Information (Box 73, Folder 7)
  - Choice 99 [1999.05]: Shipping Information, Deinstallation, 1999 - 2000 (Box 73, Folder 8)
  - Choice 99 [1999.05]: Curator/Artist File - Janine Antoni (Box 73, Folder 9)
  - Choice 99 [1999.05]: Curator/Artist File - Nan Goldin (Box 73, Folder 10)
  - Choice 99 [1999.05]: Curator/Artist File - Jerry Kearns (Box 73, Folder 11)
  - Choice 99 [1999.05]: Curator/Artist File - Sol LeWitt (Box 73, Folder 12)
  - Choice 99 [1999.05]: Curator/Artist File - Bruce Marden (Box 73, Folder 13)
  - Choice 99 [1999.05]: Curator/Artist File - Donald Sultan (Box 73, Folder 14)
  - Choice 99 [1999.05]: Curator/Artist File - Carrie Mae Weems (Box 73, Folder 15)
  - Choice 99 [1999.05]: Press Clippings (Box 73, Folder 16)
  - Choice 99 [1999.05]: T-Shirt Design, October 22, 1999 (Box 73, Folder 17)
  - What is going on in Sarajevo? [1999.06]: Invitations, Administrative, December 5, 1999 (Box 73, Folder 18)
  - The End [2000.01]: Invitations, January 29, 2000 (Box 73, Folder 19)
  - The End [2000.01]: Press Release, January 29, 1999 (Box 73, Folder 20)
  - The End [2000.01]: Exhibition Proposal, September - November 1999 (Box 73, Folder 21)
  - The End [2000.01]: Research (Box 73, Folder 22)
  - The End [2000.01]: Exit Art History, 1999 (Box 74, Folder 1)
  - The End [2000.01]: Exhibition Calendar, 1982-2000 (Box 74, Folder 2)
  - The End [2000.01]: Exhibition Checklist, January 29, 2000 (Box 74, Folder 3)
  - The End [2000.01]: Artist Lists (Box 74, Folder 4)
  - The End [2000.01]: Historical Documentation Checklist (Box 74, Folder 5)
  - The End [2000.01]: Price List (Box 74, Folder 6)
  - The End [2000.01]: Guide to Exhibition, January 29, 2000 (Box 74, Folder 7)
  - The End [2000.01]: Wall Text/Signs (Box 74, Folder 8)
  - The End [2000.01]: Exhibition Preparation/Installation Information (Box 74, Folder 9)
  - The End [2000.01]: Shipping Information (Incoming) (Box 74, Folder 10)
  - The End [2000.01]: Insurance Information and Claims (Box 74, Folder 11)
  - The End [2000.01]: Loan Information, Artists A - E (Box 74, Folder 12)
  - The End [2000.01]: Loan Information, Artists F - L (Box 75, Folder 2)
  - The End [2000.01]: Loan Information, Artists T - Z, 1999 - 2002 (Box 75, Folder 3)
  - The End [2000.01]: Correspondence (General) (Box 75, Folder 4)
  - The End [2000.01]: Correspondence (Funding), 1999 (Box 75, Folder 5)
  - The End [2000.01]: Correspondence (Press), 1999 - 2000 (Box 75, Folder 6)
  - The End [2000.01]: Correspondence (Artists - Alphabetical), 1999 - 2000 (Box 75, Folder 7)
  - The End [2000.01]: Deinstallation/Shipping Information (Box 75, Folder 8)
  - The End [2000.01]: Public Programs - Experimental Film Series, February - March 2000 (Box 75, Folder 9)
  - The End [2000.01]: Public Programs - Exhibition Tour, February 26, 2000 (Box 75, Folder 10)
  - The End [2000.01]: International Association of Art Critics Award, November 14, 2000 (Box 75, Folder 11)
  - The End [2000.01]: Press Clippings (Box 75, Folder 12)
  - Neo [2000.02]: Invitations, May 20, 2000 (Box 76, Folder 1)
  - Neo [2000.02]: Press Release, May 20, 2000 (Box 76, Folder 2)
  - Neo [2000.02]: Studio Visits (Box 76, Folder 3)
  - Neo [2000.02]: Research/Artist Lists (Box 76, Folder 4)
  - Neo [2000.02]: Loan Information (Box 76, Folder 5)
  - Neo [2000.02]: Shipping Information (Box 76, Folder 6)
  - Neo [2000.02]: Exhibition Checklist, May 20, 2000 (Box 76, Folder 7)
  - Neo [2000.02]: Price List (Box 76, Folder 8)
  - Neo [2000.02]: Wall Text/Signs (Box 76, Folder 9)
  - Neo [2000.02]: Correspondence (General) (Box 76, Folder 10)
  - Neo [2000.02]: Correspondence (Press) (Box 76, Folder 11)
  - Neo [2000.02]: Artist Files, A - Z (Box 76, Folder 12)
  - Neo [2000.02]: Receipts (Box 76, Folder 13)
  - Neo [2000.02]: Public Programs - The Beauty = Truth Proof, August 10 - 11, 2000 (Box 76, Folder 14)
  - Neo [2000.02]: Press Clippings (Box 76, Folder 15)
  - Paradise Now [2000.03]: Invitations, September 7, 2000 (Box 76, Folder 16)
  - Paradise Now [2000.03]: Invite Lists (Box 76, Folder 17)
  - Paradise Now [2000.03]: Publicity (Anne Edgar) (Box 76, Folder 18)
  - Paradise Now [2000.03]: Press Kit (Box 76, Folder 19)
  - Paradise Now [2000.03]: Cover Letter (Press Kit), July 19 - 21, 2000 (Box 76, Folder 20)
  - Paradise Now [2000.03]: Press Release (Art), June 2000 (Box 77, Folder 1)
  - Paradise Now [2000.03]: Press Release (Science), July 20, 2000 (Box 77, Folder 2)
  - Paradise Now [2000.03]: Exhibition Fact Sheet (Press Kit), September 9, 2000 (Box 77, Folder 3)
  - Paradise Now [2000.03]: Project Descriptions (Press Kit) (Box 77, Folder 4)
  - Paradise Now [2000.03]: Curator's Biographies (Press Kit) (Box 77, Folder 5)
  - Paradise Now [2000.03]: Science Issues Background (Press Kit) (Box 77, Folder 6)
  - Paradise Now [2000.03]: Genetic Research Timeline (Press Kit) (Box 77, Folder 7)
  - Paradise Now [2000.03]: Gene Media Forum (Press Kit) (Box 77, Folder 8)
  - Paradise Now [2000.03]: Exit Art Biography (Press Kit) (Box 77, Folder 9)
  - Paradise Now [2000.03]: Creative Time (Press Kit) (Box 77, Folder 10)
  - Paradise Now [2000.03]: Images (Press Kit), September 9, 2000 (Box 77, Folder 11)
  - Paradise Now [2000.03]: Advertising (Box 77, Folder 12)
  - Paradise Now [2000.03]: Press Preview Opening, September 7, 2000 (Box 77, Folder 13)
  - Paradise Now [2000.03]: Opening Dinner, September 9, 2000 (Box 77, Folder 14)
  - Paradise Now [2000.03]: SoHo Joint Opening, July 2000 (Box 77, Folder 15)
  - Paradise Now [2000.03]: Research Materials, 2000, 2005 (Box 77, Folder 16)
  - Paradise Now [2000.03]: Exhibition Proposal, January 2000 (Box 77, Folder 17)
  - Paradise Now [2000.03]: Funding (Box 77, Folder 18)
  - Paradise Now [2000.03]: Funding - JGS Foundation (Box 77, Folder 19)
  - Paradise Now [2000.03]: Budget (Box 77, Folder 20)
  - Paradise Now [2000.03]: Guest Curators - Lookout, Inc. (Marvin Heiferman & Carole Kismaric) (Box 77, Folder 21)
  - Paradise Now [2000.03]: Exhibition Preparation Schedules, March 2000 (Box 77, Folder 22)
  - Paradise Now [2000.03]: Graphic Design/Printing Information (Box 77, Folder 23)
  - Paradise Now [2000.03]: Correspondence (General) (Box 77, Folder 24)
  - Paradise Now [2000.03]: Correspondence (Curators) (Box 77, Folder 25)
  - Paradise Now [2000.03]: Correspondence (Project Manager, Ed Leffingwell) (Box 77, Folder 26)
  - Paradise Now [2000.03]: Correspondence (Press) (Box 78, Folder 1)
  - Paradise Now [2000.03]: Exhibition Checklist (Box 78, Folder 2)
  - Paradise Now [2000.03]: Loan Information (Box 78, Folder 3)
  - Paradise Now [2000.03]: Insurance (Box 78, Folder 4)
  - Paradise Now [2000.03]: Shipping Information, 2000 - 2001 (Box 78, Folder 5)
  - Paradise Now [2000.03]: Installation Information (Box 78, Folder 6)
  - Paradise Now [2000.03]: Equipment Information (Box 78, Folder 7)
  - Paradise Now [2000.03]: Wall Text/Signs (Box 78, Folder 8)
  - Paradise Now [2000.03]: Artist Lists (Box 78, Folder 9)
  - Paradise Now [2000.03]: Artist File - Heather Ackroyd & Dan Harvey (Box 78, Folder 10)
  - Paradise Now [2000.03]: Artist File - Suzanne Anker (Box 78, Folder 11)
  - Paradise Now [2000.03]: Artist File - Dennis Ashbaugh (Box 78, Folder 12)
  - Paradise Now [2000.03]: Artist File - Aziz & Cucher (Box 78, Folder 13)
  - Paradise Now [2000.03]: Artist File - Brandon Ballengee (Box 78, Folder 14)
  - Paradise Now [2000.03]: Artist File - Christine Borland (Box 78, Folder 15)
  - Paradise Now [2000.03]: Artist File - Nancy Burson (Box 78, Folder 16)
  - Paradise Now [2000.03]: Artist File - Helen Chadwick (Box 78, Folder 17)
  - Paradise Now [2000.03]: Artist File - Kevin Clarke (Box 78, Folder 18)
  - Paradise Now [2000.03]: Artist File - Keith Cottingham (Box 78, Folder 19)
  - Paradise Now [2000.03]: Artist File - Bryan Crockett (Box 78, Folder 20)
  - Paradise Now [2000.03]: Artist File - Hans Danuser (Box 78, Folder 21)
  - Paradise Now [2000.03]: Artist File - Christine Davis (Box 78, Folder 22)
  - Paradise Now [2000.03]: Artist File - Mark Dion (Box 78, Folder 23)
  - Paradise Now [2000.03]: Artist File - George Gessert (Box 78, Folder 24)
  - Paradise Now [2000.03]: Artist File - Rebecca Howland (Box 78, Folder 25)
  - Paradise Now [2000.03]: Artist File - Natalie Jeremijenko (Box 78, Folder 26)
  - Paradise Now [2000.03]: Artist File - Ronald Jones, 1997, 2000 (Box 78, Folder 27)
  - Paradise Now [2000.03]: Artist File - Eduardo Kac, 1999 - 2000 (Box 78, Folder 28)
  - Paradise Now [2000.03]: Artist File - David Kremers (Box 79, Folder 1)
  - Paradise Now [2000.03]: Artist File - Jane Lackey (Box 79, Folder 2)
  - Paradise Now [2000.03]: Artist File - Julian Laverdiere (Box 79, Folder 3)
  - Paradise Now [2000.03]: Artist File - Iñigo Manglano-Ovalle (Box 79, Folder 4)
  - Paradise Now [2000.03]: Artist File - Karl Mihail & Tran T. Kim-Trang (Box 79, Folder 5)
  - Paradise Now [2000.03]: Artist File - Larry Miller (Box 79, Folder 6)
  - Paradise Now [2000.03]: Artist File - Steve Miller (Box 79, Folder 7)
  - Paradise Now [2000.03]: Artist File - Frank Moore (Box 79, Folder 8)
  - Paradise Now [2000.03]: Artist File - RTMark (Box 79, Folder 9)
  - Paradise Now [2000.03]: Artist File - Alexis Rockman (Box 79, Folder 10)
  - Paradise Now [2000.03]: Artist File - Bradley Rubenstein (Box 79, Folder 11)
  - Paradise Now [2000.03]: Artist File - Nicholas Rule (Box 79, Folder 12)
  - Paradise Now [2000.03]: Artist File - Christy Rupp (Box 79, Folder 13)
  - Paradise Now [2000.03]: Artist File - Gary Schneider (Box 79, Folder 14)
  - Paradise Now [2000.03]: Artist File - Laura Stein (Box 79, Folder 15)
  - Paradise Now [2000.03]: Artist File - Eva Sutton (Box 79, Folder 16)
  - Paradise Now [2000.03]: Artist File - Catherine Wagner (Box 79, Folder 17)
  - Paradise Now [2000.03]: Artist File - Carrie Mae Weems, 2000 - 2001 (Box 79, Folder 18)
  - Paradise Now [2000.03]: Artist File - Gail Wight (Box 79, Folder 19)
  - Paradise Now [2000.03]: Artist File - Janet Zweig (Box 79, Folder 20)
  - Paradise Now [2000.03]: DNAid (Creative Time Billboard Exhibition) (Box 79, Folder 21)
  - Paradise Now [2000.03]: Artist Grants Posting (Box 79, Folder 22)
  - Paradise Now [2000.03]: Flag Design (Box 79, Folder 23)
  - Paradise Now [2000.03]: Public Programs - General (Box 79, Folder 24)
  - Paradise Now [2000.03]: Public Programs - Budget (Box 79, Folder 25)
  - Paradise Now [2000.03]: Public Programs - "What Can We Expect?" Panel Discussion, September 20, 2000 (Box 79, Folder 26)
  - Paradise Now [2000.03]: Public Programs - Panel Discussion, October 14, 2000 (Box 79, Folder 27)
  - Paradise Now [2000.03]: Public Programs - Exhibition Tours (Box 79, Folder 28)
  - Paradise Now [2000.03]: Expenses/Receipts (Box 79, Folder 29)
  - Paradise Now [2000.03]: Exit Art Survey (Box 79, Folder 30)
  - Paradise Now [2000.03]: Stationary (Box 79, Folder 31)
  - Paradise Now [2000.03]: Press Clippings (Box 79, Folder 32)
  - Paradise Now [2000.03]: Media Log (Box 80, Folder 1)
  - Paradise Now [2000.03]: Exhibition Travel - Correspondence, 2000, 2004 (Box 80, Folder 2)
  - Paradise Now [2000.03]: Exhibition Travel - University of Michigan Museum of Art, March - April 2001 (Box 80, Folder 3)
  - Paradise Now [2000.03]: Exhibition Travel - Tang Teaching Museum, Skidmore College, September 15, 2001 - January 6, 2002 (Box 80, Folder 4)
  - Paradise Now [2000.03]: Exhibition Travel - Regina Gouger Miller Gallery, Carnegie Mellon, October 25 - December 15, 2002 (Box 80, Folder 5)
  - Paradise Now [2000.03]: Exhibition Travel - Newcomb Art Gallery, Tulane University, March 13 - June 15, 2003 (Box 80, Folder 6)
  - Paradise Now [2000.03]: Exhibition Travel - Williamson Gallery, Art Center College of Design, August - September 2003 (Box 80, Folder 7)
  - Coded Bodies [2000.04]: Proposal (Box 80, Folder 8)
  - Coded Bodies [2000.04]: Invitations, October 19, 2000 (Box 80, Folder 9)
  - Coded Bodies [2000.04]: Press Release, October 19, 2000 (Box 80, Folder 10)
  - Coded Bodies [2000.04]: SAWCC (South Asian Women's Creative Collection) (Box 80, Folder 11)
  - Coded Bodies [2000.04]: Artist Bios and Statements (Box 80, Folder 12)
  - Coded Bodies [2000.04]: Flyer/E-mail Text (Box 80, Folder 13)
  - Coded Bodies [2000.04]: Correspondence (Box 80, Folder 14)
  - Coded Bodies [2000.04]: Mailing Lists (Box 80, Folder 15)
  - Coded Bodies [2000.04]: Program, October 19, 2000 (Box 80, Folder 16)
  - Coded Bodies [2000.04]: Reservation List (Box 80, Folder 17)
  - Coded Bodies [2000.04]: Event Preparations (Box 80, Folder 18)
  - Coded Bodies [2000.04]: Listings (Box 80, Folder 19)
  - Coded Bodies [2000.04]: Box Office (Box 80, Folder 20)
  - Coded Bodies [2000.04]: Receipts (Box 80, Folder 21)
  - Collector's Choice [2000.05]: Invitations, November 11, 2000 (Box 80, Folder 22)
  - Collector's Choice [2000.05]: Press Releases, October 2000 (Box 80, Folder 23)
  - Collector's Choice [2000.05]: Floor Maps, November 11, 2000 (Box 80, Folder 24)
  - Collector's Choice [2000.05]: Exhibition Checklist (Box 80, Folder 25)
  - Collector's Choice [2000.05]: Price List (Box 80, Folder 26)
  - Collector's Choice [2000.05]: Collector Lists (Box 80, Folder 27)
  - Collector's Choice [2000.05]: Collector's Questionaire (Box 80, Folder 28)
  - Collector's Choice [2000.05]: Artist Lists (Box 80, Folder 29)
  - Collector's Choice [2000.05]: Collector/Artist File - Gregory Allen (Box 80, Folder 30)
  - Collector's Choice [2000.05]: Collector/Artist File - JK Brown & Eric Diefenbach (Box 80, Folder 31)
  - Collector's Choice [2000.05]: Collector/Artist File - Norman Dubrow (Box 80, Folder 32)
  - Collector's Choice [2000.05]: Collector/Artist File - Richard Ekstract (Box 80, Folder 33)
  - Collector's Choice [2000.05]: Collector/Artist File - Ray Learsy, 2000 - 2001 (Box 80, Folder 34)
  - Collector's Choice [2000.05]: Collector/Artist File - Gregory Miller (Box 81, Folder 1)
  - Collector's Choice [2000.05]: Collector/Artist File - Ann Tenenbaum (Box 81, Folder 2)
  - Collector's Choice [2000.05]: Collector/Artist File - Paige West (Box 81, Folder 3)
  - Collector's Choice [2000.05]: Loan Information, Artists A - K (Box 81, Folder 4)
  - Collector's Choice [2000.05]: Loan Information, Artists L - Z (Box 81, Folder 5)
  - Collector's Choice [2000.05]: Shipping Information, 2000 - 2001 (Box 81, Folder 6)
  - Collector's Choice [2000.05]: Expenses Invoice - David Allison Photography, December 6, 2000 (Box 81, Folder 7)
  - Collector's Choice [2000.05]: Press Clippings (Box 81, Folder 8)
  - Body and The East [2001.01]: Images (Box 81, Folder 9)
  - Body and The East [2001.01]: Invitations, 2000 - 2001 (Box 81, Folder 10)
  - Body and The East [2001.01]: Press Releases, January 20, 2001 (Box 81, Folder 11)
  - Body and The East [2001.01]: Research Materials, 2000 - 2001 (Box 81, Folder 12)
  - Body and The East [2001.01]: Moderna Galerija Ljubljana Exhibition/Museum of Modern Art [Invitations], 1998 (Box 81, Folder 13)
  - Body and The East [2001.01]: Funding, 1999 - 2000 (Box 82, Folder 1)
  - Body and The East [2001.01]: Correspondence (Ljubljana), 1999 - 2001 (Box 82, Folder 2)
  - Body and The East [2001.01]: Correspondence (General), 2000 - 2001 (Box 82, Folder 3)
  - Body and The East [2001.01]: Correspondence (Press), 2000 - 2001 (Box 82, Folder 4)
  - Body and The East [2001.01]: Travel, Accommodations (Box 82, Folder 5)
  - Body and The East [2001.01]: Loan Information (Box 82, Folder 6)
  - Body and The East [2001.01]: Installation Information, 2000 - 2001 (Box 82, Folder 7)
  - Body and The East [2001.01]: Wall Labels/Text (Box 82, Folder 8)
  - Body and The East [2001.01]: Catalogue Orders, 2000 - 2001 (Box 82, Folder 9)
  - Body and The East [2001.01]: Bosnia and Herzegovina (Box 82, Folder 10)
  - Body and The East [2001.01]: Czech Republic, 1999 (Box 82, Folder 11)
  - Body and The East [2001.01]: Croatia (Box 82, Folder 12)
  - Body and The East [2001.01]: Germany (Former GDR), 1999 (Box 82, Folder 13)
  - Body and The East [2001.01]: Hungary (Box 82, Folder 14)
  - Body and The East [2001.01]: Lithuania, 1999 (Box 82, Folder 15)
  - Body and The East [2001.01]: Moldova (Box 82, Folder 16)
  - Body and The East [2001.01]: Poland, 1999 - 2000 (Box 82, Folder 17)
  - Body and The East [2001.01]: Romania (Box 82, Folder 18)
  - Body and The East [2001.01]: Russia (Box 82, Folder 19)
  - Body and The East [2001.01]: Slovakia, 2000 (Box 82, Folder 20)
  - Body and The East [2001.01]: Slovenia (Box 82, Folder 21)
  - Body and The East [2001.01]: Yugoslavia (Box 82, Folder 22)
  - Body and The East [2001.01]: Public Programs - General, 1996, 2000 (Box 82, Folder 23)
  - Body and The East [2001.01]: Public Programs - Panel Discussion, 2000 - 2001 (Box 82, Folder 24)
  - Body and The East [2001.01]: Public Programs - Balkan Cabaret, February 2, 2001 (Box 82, Folder 25)
  - Body and The East [2001.01]: Public Programs - Exhibition Tours, 2000, 2001 (Box 83, Folder 1)
  - Body and The East [2001.01]: Press Clippings (Box 83, Folder 2)
  - Danger [2001.02]: Invitations, March 31, 2001 (Box 83, Folder 3)
  - Danger [2001.02]: Press Release, March 31, 2001 (Box 83, Folder 4)
  - Danger [2001.02]: Research Materials (Box 83, Folder 5)
  - Danger [2001.02]: Correspondence (Box 83, Folder 6)
  - Danger [2001.02]: Artist Files (Box 83, Folder 7)
  - Danger [2001.02]: Exhibition Checklist, Price List (Box 83, Folder 8)
  - Danger [2001.02]: Loan Information (Box 83, Folder 9)
  - Danger [2001.02]: Shipping Information (Box 83, Folder 10)
  - Danger [2001.02]: Installation Information (Box 83, Folder 11)
  - Danger [2001.02]: Wall Labels/Signs (Box 83, Folder 12)
  - Danger [2001.02]: Public Programs - Video Program, March 31, 2001 (Box 83, Folder 13)
  - Danger [2001.02]: Expenses/Receipts (Box 83, Folder 14)
  - Danger [2001.02]: Press Clippings (Box 83, Folder 15)
  - Danger [2001.02]: Catalogue (Box 83, Folder 16)
  - Festival of Solitude [2001.03]: Invitations, April 20, 2001 (Box 83, Folder 17)
  - Festival of Solitude [2001.03]: Press Release, April 20, 2001 (Box 83, Folder 18)
  - Festival of Solitude [2001.03]: Guest Curator - Limor Tomer (Box 83, Folder 19)
  - Festival of Solitude [2001.03]: Letters of Agreement with Performers (Box 83, Folder 20)
  - Festival of Solitude [2001.03]: Correspondence (Box 83, Folder 21)
  - Festival of Solitude [2001.03]: Exit Art Member Lists, April 18, 2001 (Box 83, Folder 22)
  - Festival of Solitude [2001.03]: Press Clippings (Box 83, Folder 23)
  - The LP Show [2001.04]: Research (Box 84, Folder 1)
  - The LP Show [2001.04]: Project Description, 2000 (Box 84, Folder 2)
  - The LP Show [2001.04]: Invitations, June 9, 2001 (Box 84, Folder 3)
  - The LP Show [2001.04]: Press Release, June 9, 2001 (Box 84, Folder 4)
  - The LP Show [2001.04]: Press Kits (Box 84, Folder 5)
  - The LP Show [2001.04]: Guest Curator - Carlo McCormick (Box 84, Folder 6)
  - The LP Show [2001.04]: Contact Lists (Box 84, Folder 7)
  - The LP Show [2001.04]: Funding, 1999 - 2001 (Box 84, Folder 8)
  - The LP Show [2001.04]: Correspondence - General, 1999 - 2001 (Box 84, Folder 9)
  - The LP Show [2001.04]: Exhibition Checklist (Box 84, Folder 10)
  - The LP Show [2001.04]: Installation Information (Box 84, Folder 11)
  - The LP Show [2001.04]: Wall Text/Signs (Box 84, Folder 12)
  - The LP Show [2001.04]: Loan Information (Box 84, Folder 13)
  - The LP Show [2001.04]: Shipping Information - Outgoing, 2002 (Box 84, Folder 14)
  - The LP Show [2001.04]: Lender File - Charlie Ahearn (Box 84, Folder 15)
  - The LP Show [2001.04]: Lender File - The Analogue Society, Lamay Photo (Box 84, Folder 16)
  - The LP Show [2001.04]: Lender File - Tiffany Anders (Box 84, Folder 17)
  - The LP Show [2001.04]: Lender File - Delphine Blue (Box 84, Folder 18)
  - The LP Show [2001.04]: Lender File - Steve Blush (Box 84, Folder 19)
  - The LP Show [2001.04]: Lender File - Dan Brown (Box 84, Folder 20)